{
    "subject": "resource/Stand_Up_and_Cheer!",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Nigel_Bruce",
    "human_readable": "Nigel Bruce stars in Stand Up and Cheer!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7014943361282349,
            "question": "In what kind of film does Nigel Bruce star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699580192565918,
            "question": "Were there other actors in Stand Up and Cheer!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.615480363368988,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Nigel Bruce."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6115115284919739,
            "question": "What is the name of the film Nigel Bruce appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5641854405403137,
            "question": "Is Nigel Bruce known for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.554438054561615,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Stand Up and Cheer!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4182785451412201,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Nigel Bruce's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2781967222690582,
            "question": "What might the plot of Stand Up and Cheer! be about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23156236112117767,
            "question": "What year was Stand Up and Cheer! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22966662049293518,
            "question": "What genre is Stand Up and Cheer! likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nigel Bruce stars in Stand Up and Cheer!",
            "html": "dbpedia_4533_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Stand Up and Cheer! released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4533_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might the plot of Stand Up and Cheer! be about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4533_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Nigel Bruce's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4533_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4533_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the triple:\n\n\"Question\": Nigel Bruce stars in Stand Up and Cheer!\n\nThe documents mention that Nigel Bruce worked in many films, including \"Stand Up and Cheer!\" (1934), among others. Therefore, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Nigel Bruce starred in the film \"Stand Up and Cheer!\" (1934), which supports the statement that Nigel Bruce stars in this movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}